You guys, welcome to another video, let's discuss our phone program.
Prudam Panels has, which we have created, okay, so you will be finding the program in
the repo, which we have, but let's explore the program first, okay.
So these are the libraries we are going to use and the dv, dv.lib, this process
contained the mini-dumb right, APA we are going to use, okay.
That's why this was here and it's a function properties, nothing there.
And first of all, we need to locate the process where the process of sitting.
So we know each process has one unique process ID, so we need to search the process, we have
used to this create tools, create tool helps, 32 snapshot in various programs before.
So it will be used for a process enumeration, it will go by one by one process process first
and process next, and it will be searching the Ls as right.
So this program is used to locate and process, okay.
So the next we have this much of functions, so before dumping an Ls as, so if we are using
CMD.exe to dump an Ls as, that current process needs have enough privilege.
We discussed the privilege before previous section, privileged escalation, like AC debug privilege,
AC impersonate privilege, okay.
So to dump an Ls as, your own process, for which process you are using to dump, like
CMD.exe, or any remote process that needs to be, that program needs some privilege, okay,
to dump an Ls as, next we will be having a create mini dump of target process, okay.
So from here we will be opening the process and we will be getting a handle, then we will
be creating a file, okay, that is a dump file, so anyway it will be sitting on the Ls
as advanced dot DMP, enter the temp directory, so we will be creating a file or modifying
the existing file, and we will be using the mini dump with full memory, okay, mini
dump with full memory function, like to dump the complete memory of an Ls as, and we will
be dumping the process, okay, this complete code will be responsible for opening, creating
the file and dumping the process, okay.
Then we have a certain main functions, and our total process will be Ls as dot exe, and
our dump file will be the dump path, so we are giving the path, we can modify the path,
which you want, but I was creating under the temp folder, okay.
So this is our privileged name, SCD bug privilege, which will be, which will be giving
here, privileged name, okay, and we will be giving a process ID under the create mini
dump, okay.
This is the, I already said we will be using a process ID, when the windows, when we open
any kind of process in Windows, it will be automatically, allocating your unique PID
for each process ID, so we need to give the process ID here, so from that we can, we will
be giving the process ID parameter, okay, process ID in the create mini dump, and we will
be dumping the file, we will be dumping the Ls as process finally, okay.
So to compile this program, it has been automatically compiled and it will be sitting under
the GitHub repo, so you can find it from here, lsdum.exe, for if you want to compile the
program, if you want to modify or do anything, so you can use the CL, CL dump Lsas.clink
and ADVAP 832 live, because we will be using certain kind of, certain kind of libraries
here, right, so we will be using the ADVAP, that it will API, and we will be outputting
the files, which we need, so let's finally, our X6482 command prompt, give the output
an lsdum.exe for that, okay.
So let me open my program in my directory, it will be in our downloads, so let me go to
an lsdum.
So I will be opening a cmd, and let us an administrator move, because I already said, we
discussed a lot of things in a privileged escalation section, right, so let me copy this, okay.
So let me redirect to the program directory, so build, start the dump now, so the single
thing you need to execute like, so you just need to give lsdum.exe, so now you can see
the minidum has been successfully created, and the operation completed successfully, let's
verify this directory, see term, so here you can find the lsdum that has been created just
now like to 1825, here you can verify the date to 1825, and to 2030, now it's a 238 am,
but the file has been created to 37 am, this is the dump file, and it's the size of the file,
so by verifying the size, you can understand the lsdum has been successfully created, okay.
So there will be an interview post in some time, so how do you verify whether the lsdum
has been successfully, okay, so your answer will be, so if you verify the size of the file,
so you can confirm if the lsdum has been successfully, okay, so here the size of the file
will be for 58, 415 KB, and the lsdum was successfully, okay, so hope you enjoyed this video and you can
use your, you can download the program, you can execute the program in any of the routine assessment,
so if you are doing, yeah, so that's all about the first video, and in upcoming sections, we will
be learn how to dig the ls, or ls, file, and we can find the credentials, okay, so hope you
enjoyed this video, we will be discussing the other lsdum techniques in our coming videos,
We hope of and we'll meet you in the next video. Bye.